

- Whippany, New Jersey
- @ rob.evanik@gmail.com
- (973) 919-5256

</>> Technologies

Front End	Back End
React	Node.js
HTML 5	Express.js
CSS 3	Mongo DB
JavaScript ES6	MySQL
Bootstrap	ORMs
Web APIs	Jest
Server side APIs	Handlebars.js

Concepts & Tools

Async Await	ООР
Heroku	MVC
Postman	Agile
	Jira
BitBucket	Git
GitHub	Unit Testing
CI/CD Pipelines	Webpack
Authentication	Encryption

Certifications & Achievements

Salesforce Developer 1
Salesforce Admin
SAFe 5 Practitioner
Professional Scum Master
2021 Rising Star Award

Connect With Me

github.com/robjameva linkedin.com/in/robertevanik

Robert Evanik

About Me

Hi my name is Rob, I am a web developer from New Jersey who loves all things tech. I specialize in full stack JavaScript and have industry experience with Salesforce Apex. Things I like include, building healthy habits, learning new things, and talking tech with fellow developers.

Experience

Jr. SFDC DeveloperNov 2021 - Present

Test LeadDec 2020 - Nov 2021



Business Development

Oct 2019 - Dec 2020



Asst. Project Manager

June 2018 - July 2019

Sogeti - Johnson & Johnson

- Develop customized solutions on the Salesforce platform
- Investigate bugs, perform root case analysis and provide solutions for all production issues
- Manage shared team monthly branch, daily deployments to higher environments, and pull request approvals
- Operate within the Scaled Agile framework
- Work with large volume of production data, execute batch data edits, and production data normalization
- Lead agile ceremonies, dev team meetings, and platform wide discussions
- · Lead offshore testing team
- Executed formal system integration testing
- Developed automated test scripts with Robot Framework
- Worked closely with the development team to design comprehensive test cases

Tore Electric

- Maintained the company wide CRM database
- Generated custom dashboards used for business decision making
- Cleaned and analyzed raw data to present findings through use of pivot tables

Hollister Construction

- Managed project data within required project management databases
- Reviewed and modified projects budget on a weekly basis
- Analyzed bids received, presented recommendations, and summarized for approval

Education

Rutgers University

Oct 2021 - April 2022

Rowan University
Sept 2016 - Jan 2018

Rowan University

Sept 2012 - May 2016

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

GPA: 3.9

Master of Business Administration

GPA: 3.9

Bachelor of Science, Marketing

GPA: 3.